Guide to the Terry Sanford Papers, 1926-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Personal/Political, 1985-1992
  - Correspondence Subject Files Subseries, 1986-1992
    - Washington Post letter: Gasoline Alley-Skeezix, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Weyerhaeuser, George: Cradle of Forestry Capital Campaign, 1990 (Box 47)
    - White, Bill: Sentencing, 1989 (Box 47)
    - White House, 1988-1992 (Box 47)
    - Wilderness Bill:
      - 1988-1991, (3 folders) (Box 47)
      - Petition, 1987-1988 (Box 47)
      - Swain County, 1991-1992 (Box 47)
    - Wildlife Stamp Collection, 1988 (Box 47)
    - Will, George: Column, 1992 (Box 47)
    - Williams, Mary Beth, 1992 (Box 47)
    - Wire stories, 1990 (Box 47)
    - Womack Hospital, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Woman's National Democratic Club, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Wright Chemical Corporation, 1988 (Box 47)
    - Yellow Dog Democrat, 1986 (Box 47)
    - Youth Ambassadors Program, undated (Box 47)
    - Youth Policy Institute: Presidential Youth Issues Forum, 1988 (Box 47)
  - Budget Subseries, 1987-1992
    Contains vouchers, payment verifications, general office supply purchase records, and mail records.
    Arranged alphabetically by subject and/or vendor.
    - Alton Buck, 1988-1989 (Box 48)
    - Archer Messenger Service, 1989-1990 (Box 48)
    - Calling cards, 1989 (Box 48)
    - Carolina Clipping Service, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Catering and room requests, 1987-1990 (Box 48)
    - CompuServe, 1988-1989 (Box 48)
    - Employees, 1989-1990 (Box 48)
    - Equipment, 1989-1991 (Box 48)
    - Express mail, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Fax, 1990 (Box 48)
    - Federal Express, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - General Services Administration, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - In-State Wats, 1989-1990 (Box 48)
    - Mail reports, 1987-1990, (2 folders) (Box 48)
    - Multi-Bill Vouchers, 1989-1990, (10 folders) (Box 48)
    - Office Expense Account, 1987-1990 (Box 48)
    - Office operations, 1991-1992 (Box 48)
    - Operating budget, 1986-1987 (Box 48)
    - Operating budget, 1988-1992, (5 folders) (Box 49)
    - Pending, 1988 (Box 49)
    - Senate Photographic Studio, 1988-1989 (Box 49)
    - Photographic studio, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Post Office, 1989 (Box 49)
    - Post Office box, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Recording studio, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Senate:
      - Recording Studio, 1988-1989 (Box 49)
      - Restaurants, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 49)
      - Stationery, 1989 (Box 49)
    - Sergeant At Arms, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - State offices equipment, 1989-1990 (Box 49)
    - Stationery, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Subscriptions:
      - Journals and magazines, 1988-1990, (4 folders) (Box 49)
      - Newspapers, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - Telecommunications, 1988-1989 (Box 49)
    - Telecommunications, 1989-1990 (Box 50)
    - Telephone:
      - ATandT, 1989 (Box 50)
      - Bell Atlantic, 1989-1990 (Box 50)
      - Calling cards (919-M43-4623), 1991-1992, (3 folders) (Box 50)
      - Employees, 1989 (Box 50)
      - GTE, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 50)
      - Mobile, 1989 (Box 50)
      - Southern Bell, 1988-1990, (4 folders) (Box 50)
      - U.S. Sprint, 1989-1990 (Box 50)
    - Travel:
      - 1990 (Box 50)
      - DC staff, 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 50)
      - NC staff, 1990-1992, (4 folders) (Box 50)
    - Travel: Senator, 1989-1992, (6 folders) (Box 51)
    - Travel vouchers:
      - DC staff, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 51)
      - NC staff, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 51)
      - Samuel H. Poole, 1991-1992 (Box 51)
      - Senator, 1988-1989 (Box 51)
    - United Parcel Service, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - U.S. Mail, 1989 (Box 51)
    - U.S. Sprint, 1989 (Box 51)
    - Wachovia:
      - 1990 (Box 51)
      - Office account, 1990 (Box 51)
    - Walsh Communications, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - Washington International, 1989 (Box 51)
    - Washington International Teleport, 1990 (Box 51)
    - Western Union:
      - 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 51)
      - Senator, 1990 (Box 51)
      - Office, 1992 (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous bills:
      - 1989-1992, (4 folders) (Box 51)
      - Senator, 1989 (Box 51)
  - Campaign Files Subseries, 1986-1987, 1990-1992 and undated
    Campaign Files Subseries contains campaign literature, position papers, clippings, correspondence, newsletters, advertising plans, fundraising information, and college campus organizing materials chiefly regarding the 1992North Carolina Senatorial election, although there is a little material for the 1986campaign.
    Organized into three categories: Campaign 1986, Campaign 1992, and Campaign: Miscellaneous. Arranged alphabetically by subject within each category.
    - Campaign 1986: (Box 52)
      - Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 52)
      - Community colleges campaign, 1986 (Box 52)
      - Issue Notebook, Vol. 1-2, (4 folders) (Box 52)
      - Swearing-in ceremonies, 1986 (Box 52)
      - Thank-yous, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - Campaign 1992:
      - Advice to Sanford memo, 1991 (Box 52)
      - Advisory Committee: N.C. Regions (Box 52)
      - Announcements, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Articles, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 52)
      - Campaign contribution records, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Campaign Council certificates, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Challenger's campaigns, 1988-1990 (Box 52)
      - Coalitions: Educational organizations, 1988-1992 (Box 52)
      - Coalitions: Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Counties (WC) visit, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Debt, 1988-1992 (Box 52)
      - Democratic coordinated campaign (Box 52)
      - Democratic National convention delegates, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 52)
      - Democratic Senators Retreat, 1989 (Box 52)
      - Democratic Steering Committee, 1991 (Box 52)
      - District meetings, 1991 (Box 52)
      - Fundraising and appearances:
        - 1991-1992 (Box 52)
        - Hugh Morton program, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Get out the vote program, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Grassroots organizations, 1991-1992 (Box 52)
      - Health concerns, 1992 (Box 52)
      - High school student involvement, 1991-1992 (Box 52)
      - Interim Committee, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Issues, projects, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Jubilee Rally, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Literature, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Mailing lists, 1992 (Box 52)
      - Mailing lists, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Media contracts, 1990-1992 (Box 53)
      - Media watch, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Miscellaneous, 1986-1992 (Box 53)
      - Political cartoons, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Position papers/statements, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Potential candidate questions, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Precinct data, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Precinct targeting for yard signs and poll workers (Box 53)
      - Presidential article, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Presidential selection process, 1991 (Box 53)
      - Presidential Primary campaign, 1988 (Box 53)
      - Radio and Print advertisements, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Receptions, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Regional N.C. campaigning, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Requests for campaign materials, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Sanford vs. Faircloth, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Schedule, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Staff and volunteer work, 1990-1992 (Box 53)
      - Students-college contracts, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Students:
        - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 53)
        - General, 1992 (Box 53)
        - Memos to campus organizers, 1992 (Box 53)
        - Position papers/statements, 1992 (Box 53)
        - Volunteer lists, 1992 (Box 53)
        - Volunteer sign-up sheets, 1992 (Box 53)
        - Voter registration, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Supporter sign-in sheets, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Terry Sanford Award for Education winners (Box 53)
      - Thank-yous, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 53)
      - Veterans support, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Volunteers:
        - 1992 (Box 53)
        - Newsletter, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Voter issues pool by city, undated (Box 53)
      - Welfare, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Women's groups and issues, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Womack groundbreaking, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Young Democrats, 1992 (Box 53)
      - Biographies (Box 54)
      - Campaign information, 1992 (Box 54)
      - Code of Ethics (Box 54)
      - Fundraiser in New York, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 54)
      - Harrison Hickman speech, 1991 (Box 54)
      - Leadership Circle program, 1989 (Box 54)
      - Thank you's for freshman tour, 1988 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Miscellaneous:
      - Democratic National Committee, 1987-1988, (3 folders) (Box 54)
      - Democratic Party:
        - Democratic Leadership Council, 1989-1991 (Box 54)
        - Democratic National Committee, 1985-1991 (Box 54)
        - Democratic Policy Council, 1988 (Box 54)
        - National Democratic Club, 1987 (Box 54)
        - North Carolina:
          - Democratic Party, 1988-1992 (Box 54)
          - National Student Delegation, ca. 1990 (Box 54)
          - Young Democrats, 1990 (Box 54)
        - Senate Democratic Caucus, 1987-1989 (Box 54)
      - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, 1987-1991, (2 folders) (Box 54)
      - Fundraising:
        - American International Group, 1992 (Box 54)
        - Angier Duke Event, 1992 (Box 54)
        - Atlanta, 1989 (Box 54)
        - Breakfast events, 1991 (Box 54)
        - Charlotte, 1991-1992 (Box 54)
        - Chicago, 1989 (Box 54)
        - Contracts, 1989 (Box 54)
        - Contributors, 1992 (Box 54)
        - Correspondence:
          - 1988-1990, (3 folders) (Box 54)
          - Martha McKay, 1991 (Box 54)
        - Dallas, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 54)
        - Durham/Orange County meeting, 1992 (Box 54)
        - Florida, 1992 (Box 54)
        - General, 1988 (Box 54)
        - New York Business event, 1992 (Box 55)
        - New York Loulette Samuels event, 1992 (Box 55)
        - Old Ebbitt Grill breakfast, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 55)
        - Out of state contacts, 1988 (Box 55)
        - Sanford breakfast, 1992 (Box 55)
        - Bill Taylor event, 1992 (Box 55)
        - Wake County list, 1992 (Box 55)
        - Washington breakfast, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 55)
        - Washington, DC: CPandL event, 1992 (Box 55)
        - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 55)
      - Presidential election, 1991-1992 (Box 55)
      - Senate:
        - Gantt/ Helms, 1990 (Box 55)
        - Other, 1990 (Box 55)
    - Democratic Party: Governor's Association, 1992 (Box 55)
  - Appointment Books Subseries, 1987-1992
    Appointment books and daily schedules of Sanford's committee meetings, civic activities, and travel plans.
    Arranged chronologically within each box.
    - 1987-1992, (9 folders) (Box 55)
    - 1988-1992,May 13, (22 folders) (Box 56)
  - Memoranda Subseries, 1987-1990
    Memoranda between Sanford and staff concerning proposed legislation.
    - Memoranda to Sanford and staff, 1987-1990, (10 folders) (Box 57)
  - Nominations Subseries, 1987-1992
    Nominations regarding judicial nominations and appointments, including biographical background information, newspaper clippings, and Sanford's notes and stands on nominees.
    Arranged alphabetically by last name of nominee.
    - Boyle, Terrence William, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Clark, Robert, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Olsteen, William L., 1991 (Box 57)
    - Sarda, Peter, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Souter, David, 1990 (Box 57)
    - Thomas, Clarence, 1991 (Box 57)
    - VIP appointments and judgeships:
      - Bork, Robert: U.S. Supreme Court, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 57)
      - Hayes, James Birchard: State Department, 1987-1989 (Box 57)
      - Nomination of Edward Carnes to the 11th Circuit Court of Appeals, 1992, (3 folders) (Box 57)
      - Smokies judgeships, 1988 (Box 57)
      - Thomas, Clarence: U.S. Supreme Court, 1991 (Box 57)
  - Advisory Boards Subseries, 1987-1992 and undated
    Requests to and from Sanford regarding his participation on advisory boards.
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - Academic committee, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Agricultural, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Alfalfa Club, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
    - Arts, 1986 (Box 57)
    - Business committee, 1988-1992 (Box 57)
    - Closeup Foundation, 1987 (Box 57)
    - Farmers, 1989 (Box 57)
    - Higher Education, 1986 (Box 57)
    - North Carolina:
      - Committees, 1987-1991 (Box 57)
      - Veterinarians, undated (Box 57)
    - Northeastern Advisory Council, 1991 (Box 57)
    - Public Policy, 1988 (Box 57)
    - Steering Committee on Finance, 1987 (Box 58)
    - Textiles, undated (Box 58)
    - TVA, undated (Box 58)
    - Watch recipients, 1987 (Box 58)
    - Western N.C. Advisory Council, 1986-1987 (Box 58)
  - Invitations Subseries, 1991
    Invitations to meetings, conferences, and receptions.
    - Travel, 1991, Jan.-Nov., (20 folders) (Box 58)
  - Personal Journals Subseries, 1986-1992
    Personal Journals reflect daily entries and are closed to patron use during Sanford's lifetime unless written approval is acquired from Sanford or authorized representative.
    - 1987-1991, July 11(RESTRICTED), (18 folders) (Box 59)
    - 1987-1991, July 11(RESTRICTED), (18 folders) (Box 60)
- Legislative Files Series, 1986-1992
  The Legislative Files Series is divided into the following subseries: Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs; Foreign Relations; Budget; Select Committee on Ethics; Environment; Appropriations; Assistant's Files; Voting Record; and Miscellaneous.
  - Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs Subseries, 1986-1992
    This subseries is divided into four sections; arrangement within each section is alphabetically by subject.
    - General Banking, 1985-1992
      Materials include committee hearings, banking legislation, correspondence, clippings, and statements about banking issues such as employee stock ownership plans, taxes, and corporate takeovers.
      - Abu Dhabi debt, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Brands takeover, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Bank New York: Irving merger, 1987-1988 (Box 61)
      - Banking correspondence, 1990 (Box 61)
      - Banking:
        - Employee Stock Ownership Plan materials, 1987-1991, (2 folders) (Box 61)
        - Foreign trade: Research, speech by John Medling, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
        - Hearings:
          - Employee Stock Ownership Plan: Testimony of
            - Robert Strickland, 1987, June26 (Box 61)
            - William H. Palmer, 1987, June26 (Box 61)
            - Russell Long, 1987, June26 (Box 61)
            - Jared Kaplan, 1987, June26 (Box 61)
            - Randy Barber, 1987, June26 (Box 61)
            - Glass-Steagall, 1987, July30 (Box 61)
          - Oversight on Improper Activities in SEC: Testimony of:
            - George D. Gould, 1987 (Box 61)
            - William Seidman, 1987 (Box 61)
          - Oversight Plan on Improper Activities in SEC: Testimony of: (Box 61)
            - Edwin J. Gray, 1987 (Box 61)
            - Robert L. Clarke, 1987 (Box 61)
            - Gary Lynch, 1987 (Box 61)
          - Tender offers:
            - Research, 1987 (Box 61)
            - Takeover legislation, 1989 (Box 61)
            - Takeover testimony of:
              - Anthony Celebrezze, 1987 (Box 61)
              - Donald Clark, 1987 (Box 61)
              - F. Daniel Bell, 1987 (Box 61)
              - H. B. Atwater, 1987 (Box 61)
              - James Martin, 1987 (Box 61)
              - Jim Edgar, 1987 (Box 61)
              - Raymond Sweeney, 1987 (Box 61)
          - Williams Act Reform: Testimony of H. B. Atwater, jr., 1987 (Box 61)
        - Meeting notices, 1987 (Box 61)
        - Members of committee, undated (Box 61)
        - Memoranda, 1987-1990 (Box 61)
        - Nominations, 1987 (Box 61)
        - Overviews, 1990-1991 (Box 61)
        - Ronald Sorini, Chief textile negotiator, 1989 (Box 61)
        - Statement by Alan Greenspan 1990, July 28 (Box 61)
        - Textile memo: N.C. Textile and Apparel leaders, 1988, Sept. 9 (Box 61)
        - Textile Legislation, 1990 (Box 61)
      - Bankruptcy issues, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 61)
      - B.A.T. Industries, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 61)
      - Beazer-Koppers takeover, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Boskin confirmation hearings, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Breeden confirmation hearings, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Burlington complaints, 1987 (Box 61)
      - Burlington:
        - Layoffs, 1987 (Box 61)
        - Oversight, 1987 (Box 61)
      - Capital Markets competition, 1990 (Box 61)
      - Clark Equipment Customs, 1989 (Box 61)
      - Coin Bill:
        - 1990 (Box 61)
        - Indian housing, Canada free trade materials, 1988 (Box 61)
      - Commercial papers, 1986-1987 (Box 62)
      - Committee Hearing on Insurance Company Failures, 1992 (Box 62)
      - Cone Mills ESOP, 1991 (Box 62)
      - Corporate takeover:
        - 1988-1989 (Box 62)
        - Amendments, 1987-1989, (2 folders) (Box 62)
        - Articles, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 62)
        - Bills
          - 1987-1990, (3 folders) (Box 62)
          - Amendments, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 62)
        - Correspondence, 1987-1989, (3 folders) (Box 62)
        - Dear Colleague, 1988 (Box 62)
        - Hearing/Testimony, 1987-1990, (6 folders) (Box 62)
        - Memorandum, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 62)
      - Corporate takeover: (Box 63)
        - One share/One vote, 1988 (Box 63)
        - Speeches/statements, 1987-1990, (3 folders) (Box 63)
        - Speeches/Talking Points, 1989 (Box 63)
        - State laws/regulations, 1988 (Box 63)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 63)
      - Credit card cap, 1991 (Box 63)
      - Credit crunch, 1991 (Box 63)
      - Cummins, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 63)
      - Deferred loan losses, 1989 (Box 63)
      - Delaware law, 1987-1988 (Box 63)
      - Directors and Officers Liability, 1987-1989 (Box 63)
      - Dodd Bill, 1990 (Box 63)
      - D.P.A. Securities Enforcement Fair Trade in Financial Services markup, 1990, (3 folders) (Box 63)
      - Drexel case, 1990 (Box 63)
      - Drexel hearing (Box 63)
      - Eastern Airlines takeover, 1988 (Box 63)
      - Electronics Industry issues, 1986-1989 (Box 63)
      - Early Resolution Assisted Mergers, 1992, Feb.-Mar., (4 folders) (Box 63)
      - Elox S.337, 1990 (Box 63)
      - Employee Stock Ownership Plan, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 63)
      - Employee Stock Ownership Plan: (Box 64)
        - 1987-1990, (3 folders) (Box 64)
        - Central America, 1987-1988 (Box 64)
        - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 64)
        - Monetary Policy, 1988 (Box 64)
        - Reports, 1991 (Box 64)
      - Export-Import Bank, 1992 (Box 64)
      - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1991, Sept.-Oct., (2 folders) (Box 64)
      - Fair Trade, 1990 (Box 64)
      - Fieldcrest-Cannon Hearing:
        - Administrative details, 1991 (Box 64)
        - Background, 1986-1991, (2 folders) (Box 64)
        - Press clippings, 1991 (Box 64)
        - Witness testimony, 1991 (Box 64)
      - Foreign bank rollups, 1991 (Box 64)
      - Foreign deposits, 1989 (Box 64)
      - Freddie Mac stock/ D'Amato bill, 1986-1988 (Box 64)
      - Funds Transfer bill, 1985 (Box 64)
      - Furniture bill, 1987 (Box 64)
      - FSLIC/FDIC merger, 1984-1987 (Box 64)
      - FSUC floor action, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 64)
      - Government check cashing, life line, 1988-1991 (Box 64)
      - Great Lakes Carbon Corporation, 1987 (Box 64)
      - Hearing on the Impact of Life Insurance Company Failures on the Pensions of Working Americans, 1991 (Box 64)
      - Hodges, Luther, 1991 (Box 64)
      - House Committee on Energy and Commerce, 1987-1988 (Box 64)
      - Insurance Amendment, 1988 (Box 65)
      - Interstate banking, 1990-1992 (Box 65)
      - IRS correspondence, 1988 (Box 65)
      - Kemp, Jack: HUD nomination, 1988-1989 (Box 65)
      - Lender liability, 1991 (Box 65)
      - Leverage Buy-Outs:
        - Articles/Newspapers, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
        - Bills/Amendments, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
        - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
        - Legislation, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
        - Memorandums, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
        - Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
      - Lindsey, Lawrence: Federal Reserve Board nomination, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 65)
      - Minorco: Consolidated Gold Fields, 1989 (Box 65)
      - Monetary policy, 1991 (Box 65)
      - Mutual funds, 1979-1991 (Box 65)
      - N.C. banks, 1987-1991, (2 folders) (Box 65)
      - NCNB:
        - NCNB/CandS, 1989 (Box 65)
        - First Republic merger, 1988-1992 (Box 65)
      - NCR/ATandT takeover, 1991 (Box 65)
      - N.C. Federal SandL/Home Loan Bank Board, 1987 (Box 65)
      - N.C. Savings and Loans, 1989-1992 (Box 65)
      - Newmont Mining Takeover Amendment, 1987 (Box 65)
      - One Shore, One Vote, 1987-1989 (Box 65)
      - Pan American SandL, 1989 (Box 65)
      - Patents, 1989 (Box 65)
      - Penny stocks, 1989 (Box 65)
      - Pension bills, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 65)
      - Pension legislation, 1988-1992 (Box 66)
      - Pensions S.1679, 1991 (Box 66)
      - Possible floor amendment, 1989 (Box 66)
      - Prompt Payments Act, 1988 (Box 66)
      - Press clips, 1987-1988 (Box 66)
      - Program trading, 1987-1990 (Box 66)
      - Proportionate Liability, 1992 (Box 66)
      - Proxy rules, 1989-1991 (Box 66)
      - Public Utility Holding Company Act, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 66)
      - Rebate language, ca. 1989 (Box 66)
      - Rent To Own Bill, 1988 (Box 66)
      - Reeves Brothers takeover, 1987 (Box 66)
      - Resolution Trust Corporation:
        - 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 66)
        - Funding Act of 1992, 1992 (Box 66)
        - Markup, 1992, Feb.-Mar. (Box 66)
      - Risk Based Capital, 1987-1988 (Box 66)
      - Risk Based Premiums, 1990 (Box 66)
      - RJR-LBO Bill S.325, 1988-1990 (Box 66)
      - RTC funding, 1990 (Box 66)
      - Ruder SEC Nomination, 1987 (Box 66)
      - Sanford letters/issue, 1989 (Box 66)
      - Savings rates, 1989 (Box 66)
      - S.648 Mark-up, 1989, (3 folders) (Box 67)
      - S.824: Emergency Bank Investment Fund Act, 1991 (Box 67)
      - SEC Fraud Litigation, 1992, (2 folders) (Box 67)
      - Short-Short Rule, 1991 (Box 67)
      - Scotland County Banks, 1987 (Box 67)
      - Short selling:
        - Hearings, testimonies, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 67)
        - Memorandums, 1990 (Box 67)
        - Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 67)
      - Signature guarantee, 1982-1990 (Box 67)
      - South Africa Banking, Duty Remission, 1988-1989 (Box 67)
      - Square D, 1991 (Box 67)
      - State laws, 1987 (Box 67)
      - State powers, 1990-1991 (Box 67)
      - Takeover correspondence, 1989 (Box 67)
      - Takeover/Leveraged Buyout, 19901 (Box 67)
      - Tax Exempt Bonds, 1987-1989 (Box 67)
      - Tax Reform letters, 1986-1987 (Box 67)
      - Tax statements, 1987 (Box 67)
      - Technology changes for banks, 1987 (Box 67)
      - Third World debt, 1988-1989 (Box 67)
      - Thrift Holdings Companies Bill, 1987--1988 (Box 67)
      - Trade Enhancement Act of 1987 (Box 67)
      - Trust Indenture Act., 1989 (Box 67)
      - Truth in Savings Act, 1987 (Box 67)
      - Women in Housing and Finance speech, 1991 (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous, 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - Subcommittee on International Finance and Monetary Policy, 1986-1992
      The bulk of this section focuses on United States trade with foreign countries. Includes legislation issues such as NAFTA and GATT.
      - American Chamber of Commerce, 1991 (Box 67)
      - Arcon Manufacturing, 1992 (Box 68)
      - Arrangements: Steel Voluntary Restraint Bill, 1989 (Box 68)
      - Articles: Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 68)
      - Automotive Trade, 1991-1992 (Box 68)
      - Banking Insurance Fund, 1991 (Box 68)
      - Benzenoid dye, 1992 (Box 68)
      - Canadian beer, 1991 (Box 68)
      - Canada Trade Agreement: Park-Extraordinary Challenge Committee, 1991 (Box 68)
      - Carribean Basin Initiative, 1990-1991 (Box 68)
      - Carribean Basin Issues, S.936, 1992 (Box 68)